<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pandy</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="not_exam">THIS IS NOT A MEDICAL EXAMINATION</string>
    <string name="not_exam_text">This test is not a medical examination and hence visiting a qualified medical personeel for any medical assistance is advised.</string>
    <string name="honesty">BE SURE OF WHAT YOU RESPOND</string>
    <string name="honesty_text">You should give accurate and honest responses to the questions during the tests to receive accurate advise and assistance.</string>
    <string name="data_protect">YOUR DATA REMAINS HERE!</string>
    <string name="data_protect_text">Unless you choose to report yourself after the test / an individual(suspect), no data( or sections of it) from this phone will be uploaded to any third parties.</string>
    <string name="do_test">START TEST NOW>></string>
    <string name="select_pd">Select a Test</string>
    <string name="dr_info">Hello am doctor Pandy. I am glad to be doing this test with you and I hope that after this, you will follow the guidelines in order to stay healthy and safe.\nBut first, please choose how we are going to be interacting. Do you want to cht with me or may be u will simply click through stuff.</string>
    <string name="sft_dr_info">Hello am doctor Pandy. I am glad to be showing you the recommended safety guidelines and practices provided and obtained from the Ministry of Health and W.H.O. Do you want to view all guidelines or just those that are customised for your lifestyle/work routine? </string>
    <string name="lets_chat">LET\'S CHAT </string>
    <string name="lets_click">I WILL CLICK THROUGH THE QUESTIONS</string>
    <string name="res_cf_head">RESPONSE CONFLICT</string>
    <string name="res_cf_body">Hello there thanks for your responses but there seems to be a conflict in your responses to this question. For example, you can\'t have a strong headache and a headache, you have to choose one.</string>
    <string name="res_nt_head">DO YOU STILL FEEL THE SYMPTOM?</string>
    <string name="res_nt_body">Hello there, if you have taken tabs and you still have a strong symptom or a mild one, you need to specify. For example, if you have taken tabs and your headache is still strong or it was weak and is still weak, you need to tap that you have a strong headache or a weak one first.</string>
    <string name="rsk_cf_body">Hello there, thank you for your responses but there seems to be a conflict in your responses to this question. Yo should only select one response please.</string>
    <string name="quit_test_head">DO YOU WANT TO QUIT TEST?</string>
    <string name="quit_test_body">Hello the test is still ongoing, we need more responses from you. But you can quit now and do the test later but it won\'t be saved to this device.</string>
    <string name="res_positive">URGENT MEDICAL TEST REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="res_suspect">MEDICAL TEST RECOMMENDED</string>
    <string name="res_negative">YOU SEEM OK!</string>
    <string name="no_recomm">Hello there, thank you for your time. Unfortunately, we have not included the recommended treatment and the things you can do in order to treat or reduce on the selected symptom. Such recommendations will be availed in the future versions of the app. Don\'t forget to visit the doctor about this symptom though.Thank you.</string>
    <string name="no_recomm_rsk">Hello there, thank you for your time. Unfortunately, we have not included the recommended procedures and the methods for practicing the selected guideline. Such recommendations will be availed in the future versions of the app. Don\'t forget to put this guideline into action though, in any way you can.Thank you.</string>
    <string name="res_quit_head">DO YOU WANT TO QUIT VIEWING RESULTS?</string>
    <string name="res_quit_body">Hello your results are ready and are being displayed. Do you want to close everything and return to previous screen?</string>
    <string name="tap_for_dt">Tap to view more details</string>
    <string name="tap_for_tr">Tap to view treatment information</string>
    <string name="tap_for_gdl">Tap to open guideline</string>
    <string name="gdl_show_all">SHOW ALL GUIDELINES</string>
    <string name="gdl_show_custom">SHOW CUSTOMISED GUIDELINES</string>
    <string name="show_all">SHOW ALL ITEMS</string>
    <string name="gdl_quit_head">DO YOU WANT TO QUIT READING GUIDELINES?</string>
    <string name="gdl_quit_body">Hello do you want to close the guidelines and safety tips your are viewing right now?</string>
    <string name="acc_query_head">PANDY ACCOUNT REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="acc_query_body">Hello there, you need to create an account to continue. Through an account, we can track and store your health records and you will be ale to access our advanced services like scheduling an appointment with a doctor, or communicating with doctors directly. Do you want to create an account now?</string>
    <string name="dob_sel">Select date of birth</string>
    <string name="acc_head">Create Account</string>
    <string name="acc_body">Hello thanks for all the information you have given us. Do you want to submit this information to our data center so that a Pandy account can be created for you? </string>
    <string name="keep_info_head">YOU CAN CREATE LATER</string>
    <string name="keep_info_body">Your information has been stored on this device. It will be used to better your interaction with the App\'s services. You can create a Pandy account later if you choose.</string>
    <string name="acc_quit_head">DO YOU WANT TO QUIT CREATING AN ACCOUNT?</string>
    <string name="acc_quit_body">Hello do you want to quit creating a Pandy account? You will miss out on the health services like scheduling checkups and ordering for medicine from nearby pharmacies.</string>
    <string name="tsk_1_head">CREATE A PANDY ACCOUNT</string>
    <string name="tsk_1_body">Hello, good day! I just wanted to remind that you should create a Pandy Account. With this account, you can access the following services:\n-Scheduling appointments with doctors\n-Talking to doctors directly\n-Joining a Pandy Circle where you can share ideas with fellow patients and doctors\n-Buying medication online\n-And so much more\nJust tap \"CREATE NOW\" to continue</string>
    <string name="tsk_2_head">JOIN A PANDY CIRCLE</string>
    <string name="tsk_2_body">Hello, good day! I just wanted to remind that you should join a Pandy Circle. A Pandy circle is just a group of citizens in which you can access the following services:\n-Scheduling appointments with doctors\n-Talking to doctors directly\n-Virtual health seminars and workshops\n-And so much more\nJust tap \"JOIN NOW\" to continue</string>
    <string name="tsk_3_head">TAKE A \"RISK\" TEST</string>
    <string name="tsk_3_body">Hello, good day! I think you should take a Risk of Contraction Test. With this test, you can get to know the following about yourself:\n-Your chances of getting infected with a certain disease\n-Your chances of NOT getting infected with a certain disease\n-How hard you are trying to prevent infection\n-How you can improve your routine to reduce chances of infection. Just tap \"TAKE THE TEST\" to continue</string>
    <string name="tsk_4_head">DO A PERSONAL CHECKUP</string>
    <string name="tsk_4_body">Hello, good day! I believe you should perform a quick person checkup. With this checkup, you can get to know the following about yourself:\n-The chances that you are infected by a certain disease\n-Why you are experiencing certain symptoms.\n-What you can do to treat certain symptoms\n-An evaluation of how your body is doing against certain disease.\nJust tap \"DO THE CHECKUP\" to continue</string>
    <string name="tsk_5_head">READ SOME SAFETY</string>
    <string name="tsk_5_body">Hello, hope you are feeling OK! I just wanted to remind that you should read the Safety Guidelines. \nIn order to stay safe, you need to know how to live in your environment while ensuring that you do not get infected by contagious disease.\nJust tap \"READ NOW\" to continue</string>
    <string name="cr_warn">Hello, thank you for choosing to report a disease case. You can either report yourself if you feel infected or another individual who you think may have the disease. You must be fully certain of all the information and responses you give us. If it is discovered that you had malicious intent for reporting to us, you will be prosecuted legally and banned permanently from using this service. By selecting to report yourself or an individual, you agree to the Terms and Conditions for using this service.</string>
    <string name="cr_vct_head">BEFORE YOU BEGIN</string>
    <string name="cr_vct_body">Before you give in/submit any information regarding the person you are reporting or yourself, you need to first ensure that such information is accurate to the best of your knowledge, do not lie or give information if you have malicious intention, there are serious legal consequences if you do this. You will also be permanently banned from this service. Do you wish to continue?</string>
    <string name="self_symp_head">QUICK TEST REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="self_symp_body">In order for the authorities to better handle your case, there is need for you to select a list of symptoms you are having and how they are affecting you. A list of symptoms will be presented to you now, just select the symptoms you are experiencing and press \"NEXT\" when you are done.</string>
    <string name="dev_cll_head">DEVICE INFORMATION REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="dev_cll_body">We also need to collect information about this device you are using to report the case. This information will be used to better establish your location and also validate this report you are making. Do you want your device\'s information collected?</string>
    <string name="perm_req_head">SOME PERMISSIONS REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="perm_req_body">The app needs permission to access some details about your phone. Please grant them first or allow the app to actually access these details by simply press \"ALLOW\" when prompted.</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_1">My Tabs</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_2">Dragula Service</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_3">Pandy Circles</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_4">My Doctors</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_5">My Clinics</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_sub_1">Check on how you are following prescription and treatment</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_sub_2">Order for medication online from drug shops and pharmacies on the network</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_sub_3">See what\'s in your circles</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_sub_4">Reach out to doctors on the network</string>
    <string name="pdc_menu_sub_5">View health records at hospitals/clinics you\'ve been</string>
    <string name="no_circles">You have not joined any Pandy circles yet. You should join one now!</string>
    <string name="no_tabs">You have not added any information about how you are receiving treatment or taking your medicine. Add that information such that the app can help you keep track of your treatment activities.</string>
    <string name="no_dragula">You have not ordered any medication using this service. You can order now if you are ready.</string>
    <string name="no_doctors">You have not communicated to any doctors on this network. If you would like to, press \"START NOW\".</string>
    <string name="no_clinics">You have not been logged to any clinics on the Pandy network. If you visit these clinics and you records are logged, they will appear here.</string>
</resources>
